Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials OS
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Certificates, Diplomas, and Proclamations
  - Subseries A: Awards and Certificates
    - Class of 1917: American Field Service in France Certificate (donated ambulance), 1918 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Class of 1917 Presidential Citation, entered on the Roster of Honor, 1959 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Collins, G. Rowland: award of distinction for 25 years serving NYU, dedication Violet announcement from students of School of Commerce, and retirement proclamation, 1951-1952, 1959 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Eta Mu Phi: Charters (2), 1922, 1939 (Box 14)
    - Pi Lambda Theta, Rho Chapter: Charter, May 31, 1924 (Box 14)
    - Delta Zeta Sorority Affirmation, 1941 (Box 14)
    - Greetings from Metropolitan and Westchester Chapters of the NY State Society of Professional Engineers to NYU College of Engineering, 1955 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - Greetings to Other Universities: Blank, Tufts University, and Catholic University, 1939, 1976, undated (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - J. Hester congratulations for his inauguration as President of New York University, circa 1962 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - Scroll of Honor to NYU from Histadruth Ivrit of America, 1955 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Education by Radio and Television: Award to Radio Department for "The Dream that Grew", 1954 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Mayoral Proclamation of NYU Week, October 13-20, 1981 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - Mayoral Proclamation of NYU Kick off "Celebration 2000" year-long celebration of millennium, October 8, 1999 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - NYU Millennium Time Capsule contents list, October 8, 1999 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - NYU College Prize Certificate (8 copies to different high schools), 1893 (Box 14)
    - Men in Finance Award, March 31, 1959 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
    - Oliva, L. Jay. Proclamation honoring him on NYU Presidency, from Council of City of New York; and poster of Ireland House, 1991 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Sprague, Chaplain Ezra: Military Decoration, May 5, 1891 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Testimonial for Charles Butler LL.D. for 55 years of service to NYU and hand drawn maps of town blocks and Orleans County, 1846-1864, 1892 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2, Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
    - Violet Dedication, 1951 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 12)
    - World's Fair, 1904: NYU Gold Medal Award, circa 1904 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 12)
    - NYS Legislative Resolution Honoring NYU, March 3, 2003 (Oversize OS Box 2)
      Scope and Contents
      2003 Legislative Resolution honoring John Sexton and NYU's dedication to the community of New York City, signed by June Egeland (clerk).
    - Certificate of Incorporation, New York University Law Alumni Association, 1940 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - New York State Senate-Assembly: Act, presented to President John C. Sawhill, 1979 (Box 15)
    - New York State Assembly Resolution 1786, 2000 (Box 15)
    - NYU Press various award certificates (4), 1994-1998 (Box Shared University Archives 126)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition in St. Louis awards gold medal to NYU for model of the university campus: certificate, 1904 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Mayoral proclamation for Heights Colleges Homecoming Day, 1964-06-06 (Box Shared University Archives 046, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B: Diplomas
    - Blank Diploma: Sample, 1800s (Box 14)
    - Blank Diploma: Sample, 1980s (Box 14)
    - Blank Diploma: Sample Honorary Degree, undated (Box 14)
    - Engraving Plate of Bellevue Diploma, 1883 (Box 15)
    - Unidentified Diploma: Austria, 1831 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Unidentified Diploma: Parma, Italy, 1735 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Unidentified Diplomas: Medical Degree, 1860 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Unidentified Diplomas: Medical Degree, 1860 (Box 14)
    - Botein, Herman William: Dental School diploma, 1893 (Box 14)
    - Brown, Elmer Ellsworth: Honorary LL.D. (Doctor of Law), 1934 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 1)
    - Butler, Emily Ogden: Master of Arts (Literature, Humanities), 1902 (Box 14)
    - Drayton, Henry: Legum Bacaleurae (Doctor of Law), 1861 (Box 14)
    - Drayton, Henry: Master of Arts, 1866 (Box 14)
    - Dudek, Aliriam: M.Ph., 1896 (Box 14)
    - Dudet, Alice: Ph.D., letter, and business card, 1899 (Box 14)
    - Edmondson, T.D.: Ph.D. (Clark University), 1896 (Box 14)
    - Francis, S. W.: Honorary Membership, New York Topographical Society, 1849 (Box 14)
    - Francis, S. W.: Certificate of attendance to surgical and pathology classes and member of surgical staff, circa 1860-1865 (Box 14)
    - Francis, S. W.: Medical Department Certificate of Hon. [Honor], 1859 (Box 14)
    - Francis, Samuel W: Doctor of Medicine, 1859-1860 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Francis, S. W.: Diploma: Analytical and Practical Chemistry, 1860 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Francis, S. W.: Doctor of Medicine, 1860 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Francis, S. W.: Certificate of Residency, 1862 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Francis, S.W.: Certificate of Resident Fellow [Fellowship], 1864 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Gardiner, William Henry: Bachelor of Arts, 1843 (Box 14)
    - Gardiner, William Henry: Doctor of Medicine, 1867 (Box 14)
    - Gatlin, Carolum Mortimer: Bachelor of Arts, 1848 (Box 14)
    - Gatlin, U.W. Stuyvesant: Bachelor of Arts, 1848 (Box 14)
    - Gillet, William K.: Doctor of Humanities (Huron College), 1913 (Box 14)
    - Gillet, William: French diploma from Beaux Arts, 1914 (Box 14)
    - Greacen, John: Bachelor of Arts, 1838 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Heath, Allen S.: Doctor of Medicine, 1844 (Box 14)
    - Johnson, E.A.: Ph.D., 1862 (Box 14)
    - Maguire, James Henry: Doctor of Medicine, 1886 (Box 14)
    - Megie, Burtis C.: Bachelor of Arts, 1835 (Box 14)
    - Metropolis Law School Diplomas (Simon Loring and Edward Salinger), 1895 (Box 14)
    - McCallum, Samuel: M.D., 1879 (Box 14)
    - Millard, Charles W.: Bachelor of Arts, 1893 (Box 14)
    - Millard, Charles W.: Bachelor of Law, 1896 (Box 14)
    - Rose, Alfredum: Bachelor of Arts, 1843 (Box 14)
    - Rose, Alfredum: Master of Arts, 1846 (Box 14)
    - Stowell, D.P.: Doctor of Medicine, 1862 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Van Dyck, E. D.: Bachelor of Arts, 1880 (Box 14)
    - Van Dyck, E. D.: Master of Arts, 1883 (Box 14)
    - Van Reypen, G. R.: Master of Arts, 1861 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Van Reypen, W. H.: Doctor of Medicine, 1862 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Wood, R. A.: Bachelor of Science, 1915 (Box 14)
    - Taylor, Frederic: diploma for medical school, 1860 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Unidentifed Diplomas: Medical degree, 1840 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer: Harvard University PhD Diploma, 1924 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer: Harvard University Diploma, 1917 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer (W.S.), Francisco Franco Bahamonde Commander Diploma, 1944 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer (W.S.): New York Historical Society certificate, 1940 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - Cook, Walter William Spencer: Certificate designated a delegate from US Department of State, 1939 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
    - Samuel Slutzky diplomas and certificates re dental school, 1916-1924 (Box Shared University Archives 047, Folder 1)
- Series V: Images and Photographs
  - Unidentified Modern Building with World Trade Center in Background, circa 1973-2001 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
  - Print of a drawing of Loeb Student Center by Al Repple, given as gift for contributions to the building, circa 1950s-1960s (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Begrisch Hall, interior: photograph, undated (Box Shared University Archives 047, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, photograph, circa 1995 (Box 1)
  - Washington Square towards Loeb Student Center; NYU South Building entrance; street view of Nichols Hall; and Brookdale Hall artist rendering, 1973, undated (Box 17)
  - Chase, Chancellor Harry Woodburn, 1943 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1915: panorama photograph of class with university buildings behind them, circa 1915 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
  - Class of 1931: Panorama photograph featuring 20th Reunion of Heightsmen (class of '31), May 26, 1951 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
  - Decorative Column Capitals, undated (Box 1)
  - Dunking Pond, undated (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - "Views of New York - University" Building - Exterior, Henry Hoff view (reproduction of engraving), 1850 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Original University building and Reformed Dutch Church (photograph of engraving), 1850 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Washington Square area: Grace Church and Rectory by J. Bornet (reproduction of engraving), 1850 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Washington Square East: NYU old main building and Dutch Reformation Church (enlarged photograph), 1891 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Waiting for Parade of the Seventy-First Regiment Returns from Cuba, Lower 5th Avenue (Photograph), circa 1899 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Washington Square Buildings (photo reproduction of engraving), undated (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Exhibition: photographs of layout of material in cases. "NYU Historical Collection: Proof Sheets of Exhibition", undated (Box 15)
  - Exhibitions: "Treasures of New York University" and on Spanish Civil War., 2002-2007 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Exhibition: Grey Art Gallery Triangle Shirtwaist Fire exhibit installation photograph, 2015 (Box 10)
  - Fillmore East photograph, 1970s (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 4)
  - Frank H. Sommer (Law Alumni Association), 1942 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - Hester, James (NYU President): Inauguration (8 photographs), October 25, 1962 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
  - Historical Interiors and Exteriors: NYU Photo Bureau Prints, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Glee & Musical Club Members: group photograph, 1921-1922 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Glee Club and Hall of Fame Singers: group photograph, December 12, 1942 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Glee Club Concert: 23rd Annual Town Hall Concert, 1952 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
  - Glee Club and Radcliffe Choral Society during 24th Annual Town Hall Concert: group photographs, December 11, 1953 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Glee Club Camp in Pocono Pines, PA: group photograph with name list, September 8-15, 1963 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Glee Club Camp at Pocono Pines, PA: group photograph with name list, September 9-13, 1966 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Glee Club Town Hall Concert with Simon's College girls: photograph of Glee Club performing E. Jon de Revere conducting, December 8, 1967 (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Metallurgy laboratory, undated (Box Shared University Archives 047, Folder 7)
  - NYU Washington Square Center Guide to University Locations, undated (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Office of Radio and TV (In studio, three men discussing notes, with camera), circa 1955-1960 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - "Biochemistry laboratory for first-year students: problems in nucleic acid chemistry" (photograph with caption), undated (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 2)
  - "Dr. Allan E. Dumont of the department of surgery instructs student in suturing procedures in trauma service" (photograph with caption), undated (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 4)
  - "Philomanthian Hall" interior classroom; exterior with students of La Maison Francaise; and exterior unknown NYU buildings, circa 1895-1980 (Box 17)
  - Military Parade Ground (print of painting), 1851 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 16)
  - Sawhill, John, undated (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - School of Commerce: Class of 1906 (Box 7)
  - School of Commerce: First annual dinner, Class of 1915 (Box 6)
  - School of Commerce: Class of 1916 dinner, 1914 (Box 6)
  - School of Commerce: Class Dinner, 1916 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
  - School of Commerce: Class of 1917, 10th Reunion, 1927 (Box 7)
  - School of Continuing Education: Adult Degree Studies Faculty, 1994 (Box 1)
  - School of Law, Afternoon Division (Class of 1923), circa 1923 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
  - School of Law (Class of 1924) (Box 7)
  - Seals of the University (photographs), 1953, 1956 (Box 15)
  - Sniffen, D. Austin, [President], 1937-1939 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - Kevorkian Center/Kuwwatli House, Damascus, 1967-1976 (Flat-file-folder 4, Drawer 7)
  - Lipton Mast, undated (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 2-3)
  - Model of Warren Weaver Hall, undated (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Warren Weaver Hall (?) colored ink drawing by Christine Pappas, 2000 (Box 17)
  - Baseball Team 1910 season (Box 7)
  - Baseball team 1914 season (Box 7)
  - Baseball team, circa 1890s (Box 7)
  - Football team, 1897 (Box 6)
  - Football team, 1902 (Box 6)
  - Football team, 1904 (Box 6)
  - Football team, 1910 (Box 6)
  - Football team, circa 1910 (Box 6)
  - Football team, circa 1920s (Box 6)
  - Football team, 1922 (Box 6)
  - Football team: "Those Wilted Violets" sketches with Mal Stevens, by Gus Uhlmann, circa 1934-1941 (Box 17)
  - Football team: "NYU Drops Football" cartoon sketch by Gus Uhlmann, undated (Box 17)
  - Athletics (football, basketball, track) sketches, along with World Telegraph clippings attached. 4 sketches, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Glee Club Town Hall with Smith College, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Glee Club Town Hall, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity (Fuji) group member photographs (24 prints), 1904-1917 (Box 32)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity, 1913 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity, circa 1920s (Box 6)
  - Law Alumni Class of 1915 27th Anniversary dinner at Longchamps, April 16, 1942 (Box Shared University Archives 122)
  - Graduate School of Business, Spring Dinner Money Marketeers Downtown Athletic Club, June 2, 1948 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
  - Graduate School of Business, Annual Dinner, Money Marketeers Downtown Athletic Club, May 26, 1949 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
  - Graduate School of Business, Spring Dinner Money Marketeers Downtown Athletic Club, May 31, 1950 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
  - Heights Senior Ball photograph, Plaza Hotel, 1934, 1934 May 5 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Hemmerdinger Hall: renovation photograph, undated (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Israel M. Flapan 1922 NYU School of Law Photograph (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 6)
  - Picasso Sculpture: Signed photograph, undated (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 7)
  - Student body group on Gould Memorial Library steps: photograph, 1908 (Box Shared University Archives 128)
  - Thomas L. Norton, 1955-1962 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 1)
  - Photograph: Women's Law School Class 1918 (Box Shared University Archives 122)
  - Graduate Camp (panoramic photograph) group portrait of men and women, 1950 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 3)
  - Annual Dinner of the Society of Friends of Scripta Mathmatica, Hotel Astor, May 9, 1937 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Forty-second Summer Meeting of the Mathematical Organizations of America, in Connection with the Harvard Tercentenary Celebration in Cambridge, Massachusetts (Panorama group photograph with name listings), August 31 - September 5, 1936 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Student Army Training Corps (SATC) panorama photograph of class, 1918 (Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Student Army Training Corps (SATC) panorama photograph of class, undated (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Plane/Glider in the air (reproduction of photograph, found framed, unknown origin), 1940-2015 (Box Shared University Archives 131)
  - Child sitting, wearing hat-(from RISM Collection?), undated (Box Shared University Archives 131)
  - Portrait of Thorndike Saville, faculty and Dean, with plaque, circa 1957 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Portrait of Collins Pechin Bliss, faculty and Dean, circa 1936 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Reproduction of painting of Charles P. Brush, faculty and dean, circa 1896 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Portrait of Charles Henry Snow, faculty and dean, circa 1930 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Sketch portrait of Earle B. Babcock by Gilbert (Thomas) White, circa 1935 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Panorama photographs of NYU commencement from various angles within Washington Square Park (4 images, previously framed together), circa late 1970s to 1980s (Flat-file-folder 1)
- Series VI: Clippings, Graphic Materials, and Printed Matter
  - "The Right to Refuse to Answer" (article), 1955 (Box 9)
    Original location: Florence Perlow Shientag Papers (MC 216)
  - Boston Weekly Messenger: Account of Founding NYU, June 8, 1837 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Bulletin (NYU publication), May 1, 1941 (Box 17)
  - Daily News: Commencement Article, June 6, 1980 (Box 17, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Florence Perlow Shientag Campaign Scrapbook, 1954 (Scrapbook Florence Perlow Shientag Campaign)
  - Florence Perlow Shientag Scrapbook, 1938-1955 (Box 9)
  - Flyer for Grand One Cent-ennial Exposition: Oratory of "Heroes of '76", April 12, 1875 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Gleason's Pictorial: illustration of NYU University building, Wade View, September 4, 1852 (Box 17)
  - Governor's Citation for Exhibit on Mary Baker Eddy (Laminated Reproduction), 2004 (Box 1)
    Related Materials at the NYU Archives
    RG 12.25
  - Leslie's Weekly: University Involvement in WWI Engineering and Machinery, November 12, 1918 (Box 12)
  - Map: Geological Map of New Mexico and Colorado (Professor John J. Stevenson, Geological Assistant), 1881 (Box 17)
  - Map in German, undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 1)
    Original Location: Courant Papers (MC 150)
  - Map of Manhattan (New York, NY), 1831 (Box 15)
  - Map: Historical map of Greenwich Village, July 1927 (Box 17)
  - Map: Supervue of New York- Manhattan, 1934 (Box 17)
  - Map of Northern Italy, circa 1800s (Box 38)
  - New York City Census of 1855: List of occupants in University building, June 23, 1855 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - New York Daily Tribune: Description and Photo of NYU, Apr 15, 1894 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 9)
  - New York Herald: Summer School, August 18, 1907 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - New York Herald Tribune: Hall of Fame Ceremony, May 19, 1929 (Box 17)
  - New York Herald Tribune: Photographs of Buildings to be Razed to Build Law School, June 9, 1932 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - New York Herald Tribune: Greenwich Village Buildings That Will Make Way for NYU's Law Center, February 11, 1948 (Box 17)
  - New York Metropolitan Review, April 26, 1972 (Box 12)
  - New York Mirror: description of university with building illustration, September 13, 1834 (Box 17)
  - New York Times advertisement from NYU Board: "What New York University can be, and what it cannot be.", May 30, 1972 (Box Shared University Archives 126, Folder 2)
  - New York Tribune [New York Times], November 7, 1870 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - NYU announcement of Annual Course of Instruction and Faculty (reproduction), October 3, 1836 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - NYU Alumni Reunion Weekend (print proof), 1991 (Box 38)
  - NYU Daily News, Special Christmas Section, December 23, 1925 (Box 17)
  - NYU Daily News: 100th Anniversary Issue and supplements, 1931 (Box 17)
  - NYU Bonds, coupons redeemed (1894-1920) pasted on ledger pages, circa 1894-1920 (Box 15)
  - NYU Bonds: Coupon Sheets, circa 1937 (Box 1)
  - Founder's Day logos, with individual school shields surrounding torch (proof sheet), 1991 (Box 15, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - NYU Incorporation Act, undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 17)
  - Office of Undergraduate Admissions: Logo envelope, undated
  - Pamphlet: "Within Bohemia's Borders: Greenwich Village, 1830-1930", 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Pictorial Living-Special Section: Golden Jubilee of Bronx County. (Another copy of this was placed in NYU time capsule), January 19, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Proclamation from the Executive Chamber Creating Law Day, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Program for Senior Production, 1915 (Box 38)
  - Program for Tracey/Barry Gallery Exhibition: "You Make Me Feel [Mighty Real]: The Work of Robert Blanchon", 2009-2010 (Box 1)
  - [The Richmond Whig], April 12, 1865 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Saturday Evening Post re: Sunrise semester, April 5, 1958 (Box 12)
  - Sheet Music: University Grand March, dedicated to the students of New York University, 1852 (Box 12)
  - Sheet Music: Funeral March. In Memoriam of Professor Sam F. B. Morse (Samuel Morse), 1872 (Box 12)
  - Tiffany Torch blueprints, October 18, 1911 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
  - Times Dispatch (Richmond, VA): Edgar Allen Poe, January 17, 1909 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Tisch School of the Arts -- Animation Festival Posters, 1990s-2000s (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 14, Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 14 Left)
  - The University Item, No. I, November 15, 1858 (Box 17)
  - The University Item, No. III, March 1, 1866 (Box 17, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Variety: "NYU Film School Turns 60", November 19, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Variety: "Tisch School Turns 25", October 22, 1990 (Box 12)
  - The World Magazine: "Victory Hall, New York City's War Memorial", March 14, 1920 (Box 17)
  - NYC Planning Commission: A Plan For New York City Volume 1: Critical Issues, 1969 (Volume Plan for New York City, Volume 1)
  - NYC Planning Commission: A Plan For New York City Volume 4: Manhattan, 1969 (Volume Plan for New York City, Volume 4)
  - School of Law expansion plan brochure, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Original etching of Washington Square Arch by Tony Pugliese (1928) with letter of explanation, 1928, 1951 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Washington Square Arch color lithograph, from "Greenwich Village" art portfolio by Kevin Monaghan, undated (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Color Lithograph: Mr. F.S. Chanfrau, as Mose. Resuing the child in the last scene of "New York As it Is" performed at the Chatham Theatre, N.Y., undated (Box 17)
  - Reproduction of the view of the attack against Fort Washington and rebel Redcoats, November 16, 1776, drawn by Tho. Davies, undated (Box Shared University Archives 122)
  - "Villa La Pietra, New York University, Florence, Italy" (color print), undated (Box Shared University Archives 045, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, Washington Square Park, Stage and Detail, 1994-04-07
- Series VII: List of Collections for Separated Materials
  - Records of Board of Trustees (RG 2.0) Sheet Music: "America Triumphant," and "A Prayer", circa 1951-1954 (Box 12)
  - Records of the Office of Administration and Facilities (Eileen Buckley) (RG 8.0): Washington Square Center maps/block layouts, studies of streets, etc., 1953-1965 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Records of the Office of the Treasurer (Muriel L. Mantel) (RG 10.9), 1927-1962, undated (Box 21, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 1, Box Shared University Archives 046, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 11)
    Related Materials
    These oversized materials are part of the Records of the Office of the Treasurer (Muriel L. Mantel) (RG 10.9).
  - Records of NYU College of Dentistry (RG 25): clipping, certificate, exhibition text, 1791, undated (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Records of the RISM Cross-Cultural Comparisons of Aging and Longevity Study (The Longevity Study) (RISM RG 15) (Flat-file-folder 5)